Guide to the Between C & D Archive circa 1983-1990 MSS.084
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Joel's Copy with All Variants
  - v.1, #4, var.2, 1985; Mixed Media by David Wojnarowicz (illustration of a head with lips sewn shut and barbed wire, ontop of an image of a dollar bill) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - v.1, #4, var.3, 1985; Mixed Media by David Wojnarowicz (illustration of a person holding a knife to another person's throat, ontop of an image of a dollar bill) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - v.1, #4, var.4, 1985; Mixed Media by David Wojnarowicz (illustration of a body with head split open and brains leaking, ontop of an image of a dollar bill) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - v.1, #4, var.5, 1985; Mixed Media by David Wojnarowicz (illustration of a flaming skull flying above a city in rubble, on top of an image of a dollar bill) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - v.1, #4, var.6, 1985; Mixed Media by David Wojnarowicz (illustration of a baby on fire, on top of a color photocopy of a one dollar bill) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - v.2, #1, var.1, 1985; Printed/Fabricated by Chris Costan (broken easter eggs on a textured blue background, from the right-hand egg a building emerges, and from the left-hand egg, a pot, plate, bowl and saucer are being lifted) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - v.2, #1, var.2, 1985; Printed/Fabricated by Chris Costan (three broken easter eggs, from which some carbon structures, a pineapple, and an elliptical map of the world are emerging. on top of a half-red and half-yellow background that features arabic writing.) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - v.2, #1, var.3, 1985; Printed/Fabricated by Chris Costan (two broken easter eggs, from which a triangle, a light bulb, a ruler and some clouds are emerging. on top of a textured pink background) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - v.2, #1, var.4, 1985; Printed/Fabricated by Chris Costan (two broken easter eggs, from whence a centipede and the constellation Perseus [holding the Pleiades] issue) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - v.2, #2, var.1, 1985; Salvadorian Cocktail Napkins (image - color: child with large hair - red, woman biting her finger - blue, child with flat hair - gold) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - v.2, #2, var.2, 1985; Salvadorian Cocktail Napkins (image - color: child with large hair - gold, woman biting her finger - blue, child with flat hair - red) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - v.2, #2, var.3, 1985; Salvadorian Cocktail Napkins (image - color: child with large hair - blue, woman biting her finger - red, two children standing together - gold) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - v.2, #2, var.4, 1985; Salvadorian Cocktail Napkins (absent) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - v.2, #3, var.1, 1986; Darkest Impression (otherwise identical) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - v.2, #3, var.2, 1986; Lightest Impression (otherwise identical) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - v.2, #3, var.3, 1986; Medium Impression (otherwise identical) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - v.2, #4, var.1 (mislabeled), 1986; Cover text contains the date, volume, issue, contributer, and slogan information from the previous issue (v.2 #3) but the cover art is by Kiki Smith, and the following pages contain v.2 #4's masthead, table of contents, stories and inserted material.; Front cover by Kiki Smith (anatomical illustration of human organs, predominant color is dusky pink) Inserted material by Jolie Stahl (an illustration of a woman with a sheep, with green overlay and red text) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - v.2, #4, var.2, 1986; Front cover by Kiki Smith (anatomical illustration of human organs, predominant color is yellow ochre) Inserted material by Jolie Stahl (an illustration of a woman with a sheep, with brown overlay and red text) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - v.2, #4, var.3, 1986; Front cover by Kiki Smith (anatomical illustration of human organs, predominant color is pale blue-green) Inserted material by Jolie Stahl (an illustration of a woman with a sheep, with red overlay and red text) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - v.2, #4, var.4, 1986; Front cover by Kiki Smith (anatomical illustration of human organs, predominant color is blue/purple) Inserted material by Jolie Stahl (an illustration of a woman with a sheep, with red overlay and green text) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - v.3, #1, var.1, 1986-87; Mixed Media by Deborah Root Brague (illustrations of three women and one man on top of a forest scene; captions "I'LL KILL YOU, DARLING!" "NO, DON'T!" & "I'M GOING INSANE!") (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - v.3, #1, var.2, 1986-87; Mixed Media by Deborah Rot Brague (illustrations of a head wearing a top hat and a large penis ontop of a photo of a woman in a bikini, on top of a photo of a garden; text box "THAT ISN'T MY BODY!") (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - v.3, #1, var.3, 1986-87; Mixed Media by Deborah Root Brague (illustration of a man and a woman in Victorian garb, on top of an estate lawn, which is bisected, with a starscape behind; captions "IT'S HER FAULT!" and "IT'S HIS FAULT!") (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - v.3, #1, var.4, 1986-87; Mixed Materials by Deborah Root Brague (illustration of two women in classic/al garb fighting and of a Greek statue, on top of a photo of a garden, with a starscape behind; caption "What a girl! She knew what she wanted - and she wasn't afraid to fight for it!") (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - v.3, #1, var.5, 1986-87; Mixed Materials by Deborah Root Brague (illustrations of a victorian couple and a disembodied hand holding a handkerchief, on top of a photo of a red fainting couch, on top of a starscape; caption "YES, IT'S TRUE, DEAR, I HATE YOU!") (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - v.3, #2, var.1, 1987; Print by Bonnie Lucas, from "Quality Time" (baby's bottle shooting milk and two rabbits in the foreground, a girl in a blue dress in the middleground, English garden in the background) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - v.3, #2, var.2, 1987; Print by Bonnie Lucas, from "Quality Time" (baby's bottle shooting milk and a girl's crotch in frilly shorts/underwear in the foreground, supine baby on a cushion in the middleground, floral "wallpaper" and yellow floor in the background) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - v.3, #2, var.3, 1987; Print by Bonnie Lucas, from "Quality Time" (baby's bottle shooting milk in the foreground, woman in a pink, ruffly dress in the middleground, flat blue background) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - v.3, #3, var.1, 1987; Imprint of a Painting by Orshi Drozdik (at the right foreground is a semi-dressed man embracing a resisting semi-dressed woman, who is reaching towards a chair; the background is predominantly a blue wallpaper [which contains some text] and a purple floor) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - v.3, #3, var.2, 1987; Imprint of a Painting by Orshi Drozdik (in the foreground, a man stradles a semi-prone woman, pulling her hair with one hand and the shoulder-strap of her dress with the other; the background is a predominantly pink wallpaper [which contains text] and a green floor) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - v.3, #3, var.3, 1987; Imprint of a Painting by Orshi Drozdik (in the left foreground, a man with an open shirt is forcing his way through the door of a resisting woman and grabbing her dress; the background is a predominantly green wallpaper [which contains text] and a checked pink-and-purple floor) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - v.4, #1, var.1, 1988; Sticker Sheet by Patrice Clare and Gregory Rukavina (three images of R. Budd Dwyer's suicide; loose sticker at top center) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - v.4, #1, var.2, 1988; Sticker Sheet by Patrice Claire and Gregory Rukavina (three images of R. Budd Dwyer's suicide; loose stickers in center column, top three rows) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - v.4, #1, var.3, 1988; Sticker Sheet by Patrice Claire and Gregory Rukavina (three images of R. Budd Dwyer's suicide; no loose stickers) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - v.4, #2, var.1, 1988; Illustration by Art Spiegelman (misspelled on the cover as "Art Spielgelman," but spelled correctly on masthead; images of many "average" people bound and blindfolded, standing against a brick wall) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - v.4, #2, var.2, 1988; Illustration by Art Spiegelman (misspelled on the cover as "Art Spielgelman," but spelled correctly on masthead; two punks having sex and lighting each other's cigarettes, in the left background to the left is a crowd scene in which everyone is drinking, and in the right background is an imagine of a bottle on graph paper) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - v.4, #2, var.3, 1988; Illustration by Art Spiegelman (misspelled on the cover as "Art Spielgelman," but spelled correctly on masthead; a café scene in which all characters are skeletons, including a "female" skeleton with large breasts and erect nipples, skeleton musicians, a skeleton dressed in stereotypical French artist garb with an erection standing on a table reading from a book and holding a bottle) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - v.4, #3, var.1, 1988; "Crisper" Impression - printed words distinguish themselves most clearly (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - v.4, #3, var.2, 1988; "Less Clear" Impression - printed words bleed into the paper (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - v.5, #1, var.1, 1989; Illustration by Elizabeth Brady (New York stoop-scene, in which one of the trash cans is on fire) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - v.5, #1, var.2, 1989; Illustration by Elizabeth Brady (transit scene with people holding hand-straps, person wielding a knife at the right, girl with spiral-eyes at the lower-middle-left) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - v.5, #1, var.3, 1989; Illustration by Elizabeth Brady (psychedelic taxi cab) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - v.5, #2, var.1, 1989; Mixed Media by Joy Lou G. (cherub with a needle in his arm) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - v.5, #2, var.2, 1989; Mixed Media by Joy Lou G. (cherub with a long pipe) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - v.5, #2, var.3, 1989; Mixed Media by Joy Lou G. (two cherubs making-out) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - v.5, #3, var.1, 1989; Impression of a Painting by Jane Dickson (two people standing over a playpen or crib) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - v.5, #3, var.2, 1989; Impression of a Painting by Jane Dickson (four men, two of whom are wearing large clown or dunce caps) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - v.5, #3, var.3, 1989; Impression of a Painting by Jane Dickson (many people holding hands) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - v.6, #1, var.1, 1990; Mixed Media by Joan Posluszny (triptych of Nazi material) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - v.6, #1, var.2, 1990; Mixed Media by Joan Posluszny (image of a golden suitcase containing a photo of a woman reclining in bed, and a photo of three naked women bending over) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - v.6, #1, var.3, 1990; Mixed Media by Joan Posluszny (sinister triptych) (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Series IV: Anthology
  Series IV contains one box of materials relating to the Between C & D anthology, including manuscripts, the galley, author biographies, permissions, publicity, correspondence and contracts.
  - Subseries A
    - Between C & D anthology and galley, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Bios, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Contract/royalty statements/proposal, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Covers, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Japanese edition, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts (A - F), undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts (G - P), undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Manuscripts (R - Z), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Manuscript (Between C & D anthology), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript with editor=s notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Permissions, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Proof copies (uncorrected and with editor=s notes), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Publicity and readings, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Title, contents, proposal introduction, and introduction, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: Oversize
    - Between C & D Anthology poster, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Series V: Ephemera
  Series V contains three boxes of Epson computer components, including the keyboard and monitor, and one box containing the floppy disks on which are located the print files for the magazine and anthology as well as back-up mailing lists, administrative forms, outgoing editorial correspondence and author biographies for the anthology, as well as two small gray boxes of stamp art used in the production of the magazine.
  - Four rubber stamps used for v.1, #2 and two of eight rubber stamps used for v.1, #3, undated (Box 13, Folder 1A.)
  - Six of eight rubber stamps used for v.1, #3, undated (Box 13, Folder 1B.)
  - Computer disks (floppy and zip), undated (Box 13, Folder 1C.)
  - Epson keyboard, undated; cuid5948; 1 item one computer keyboard (Box 15)
    computer equipment.
  - Epson computer, undated; cuid5949; 1 item one computer case (Box 16)
  - Epson monitor, undated; cuid5950; 1 item one computer monitor (Box 17)
- Series VI: Printed Material
  Series VI contains one box of miscellaneous printed materials arranged alphabetically. Included are various little magazines contemporaneous with Between C & D and often containing fiction by authors that appear in Between C & D.
  - Beatniks from Space, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - City Lights Review #2, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Details (v.6, #10, May 1988), undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Directory of Literary Magazines 1990-91, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - The Florida Review (v.14, #1), undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Grants and Awards Available to American Writers, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Kwadraat, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - LPvres Urbaines #10, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Pamphlets, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Mississippi Mud #29, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The 1985 Directory of Literary Magazines, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The 1989-90 Directory of Literary Magazines, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Storytellers (v.2-4), undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Style 1, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 25 Mensuel, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Oversize Box
  - Liston vs. Clay poster (1964), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - David Wojnarowicz Posters from v.1, #4, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cover art from v.6, #1, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Between C & D Anthology poster, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)